Oh hi! This video is about this bodysuit because I made this bodysuit and I'm going to show you
how I made it. However it's not a tutorial I just thought you might be interested in the whole
process. So I'm starting with selecting the color, transferring the pattern to the latex, cutting it
out gluing it together and washing it from zero to me wearing this one at the
moment I hope you're enjoying this because to be honest I love to watch
crafting videos and watch people do something craft something I think it's
completely relaxing so enjoy step number one decide on a color because I already
got several black bodysuits so I thought I'm going to go both this time
something colorful and now I have to decide which one so we got red here a
bronze and a purple there's always a backside and a front side this will be
outside of course and I think I'll go with the red one
Caught in a fragile light
Torn on a table tight
Injected fears a sad smile
Paid up and lost in yourself
Failed to donate a prize
The symptom of our lifetime
Do I love you?
She said to our love, she said, on our way down, on our way down
They don't suffer, they don't suffer
Bored in a fragile light
Torn on a weighted side
Infected fears are not to cry
Paid up and lost in yourself
Failing to recognize
The symptom of our lifetime
To a large sea, to a large sea
On a weather, on a weather
Redolphe, redolphe
Tell me the reason you brought me here
Thank you.
to
come
Make
your way
with
me
now
Do you take
this song
this voice
this breath
this dream
this sense
Just let it fall away
You're the soul inside
Just let it soar away
You'll turn on me now
I'll miss you all the time
Come on, it's alright
You're telling me
I'll miss you all the time
Forever
I'll send you down
I'll bring your love
I'll send you far
Take your life and pass me out
Do not take this all as far as you like this
Let me stay in this sad time
Just like the fall of a baby, you are the song
You're so hard to run, you're so hard to lose
You're so hard to understand, you're just getting so old
You're telling me now, it's too late, it's all right
Come what may
You'll turn up in the sunset
This indecision makes her fall down
You already turned those lights out
All right.
So I hope you enjoyed this process video.
I think it's pretty cool.
I like to watch it myself to be honest.
Yeah.
Tell me in the comments if you have any questions.
But please don't start any discussions about wearing underwear on the latex or something
like that.
I'm wearing underwear here because I'm filming a YouTube video and this is just what I do
on YouTube.
So have a nice day.
See you all around. Bye!